donnakaran.com 2019-09-06

# Privacy Policy - Donna Karan

This Privacy Policy explains how The Donna Karan Company Store LLC (collectively, “DKC”) collect and use information provided to us from your use of www.donnakaran.com and any other website, microsite, mobile device application, social media or other Internet property and related services owned or operated by DKC or its affiliates where this Policy appears (collectively, the “Sites”). By visiting and using our Sites, you agree to our collection, use and disclosure of your information as described in this Privacy Policy.

WHAT TYPES OF INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?

HOW DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION?

HOW WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION

YOUR RIGHT TO OPT-OUT.

WWHAT ARE YOUR ACCESS RIGHTS?

HOW DO WE SECURE YOUR INFORMATION?

ARE CHILDREN ALLOWED TO USE OUR SITES?

CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

POLICY UPDATES

CONTACT US

## WHAT TYPES OF INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?

INFORMATION YOU GIVE US. When you use our Sites, we may collect different types of information from you. This may include: a) information you provide directly to us; b) information related to orders you place; c) surveys and promotion entries; d) your communications with us. The information collected may include your name, e-mail address, billing address, shipping address, phone number, credit card information, birthday, login name and password, gender, and location. We also collect any information you submit or post to our Sites.

**NOTE FOR INTERNATIONAL USERS: WE STORE INFORMATION BOTH IN AND OUTSIDE OF THE UNITED STATES. If you live outside of the United States, you understand and agree that we may transfer your information to the United States. The Sites are subject to U.S. laws, which may not afford the same level of protection as those in your country.**

USAGE INFORMATION. We may collect your Internet Protocol (IP) address, Internet service provider, operating system, type of web browser, mobile or other device identification number, pages you view, and the duration of time spent on these Sites. We might look at what site you came from, or what site you visit when you leave us.

MOBILE. When you use our mobile sites, we may collect information from you which may include your location, device identification number, access to your contacts, and how often you use the site. Most mobile devices allow you to turn off these features. For information on how to do so, please visit your mobile device’s user guide.

## WE COLLECT INFORMATION IN DIFFERENT WAYS.

WE COLLECT INFORMATION DIRECTLY FROM YOU. For example, if you register with us or enter a promotion. We also collect information if you contact us.

WE COLLECT INFORMATION from you passively. We use tracking tools like browser cookies and web beacons. We do this on our Sites and in emails that we send to you. We collect information about users over time when you use this Site. We may have third parties collect personal information this way. Learn more about these tools and how you can control them here.

WE GET INFORMATION ABOUT YOU FROM THIRD PARTIES. For example, our business partners may give us information about you. Social media platforms may also give us information about you.

WE COMBINE INFORMATION. For example, we may combine information that we have collected offline with information we collect online. Or we may combine information we get from a third party with information we already have.

## HOW DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION ?

TO PROVIDE COMPLETE SERVICES. For example, we use your information to respond to your requests, to process and deliver purchases, to process returns, and to offer you products, services and features through the Sites. We may use your information to respond to your customer feedback. 

FOR MARKETING PURPOSES. For example, we may send you notices and correspond with you about products and special offers. We might tell you about new features or updates on the sites. These might be third party offers or products we think you might find interesting. To learn about your choices for these communications, read the “Choices” section below.

TO IMPROVE OUR PRODUCTS AND SERVICES. We may use your information to make our website and products better. We might use your information to customize your experience with us. We may combine information we get from you with information about you we get from third parties.

SECURITY. We may use your information to protect our company and our customers. We also use information to protect our websites and apps. This may include using your information for fraud protection or credit risk reduction purposes.

TO COMMUNICATE WITH YOU. For example, we will communicate with you about your account or our relationship. We may contact you about your feedback. We might also contact you about this Policy or our website Terms.

OTHER USES. We may use information for other reasons permitted by law or we may describe to you. We will get your consent as required by law.

## HOW WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION

We may share your information with third parties. For information on how to opt-out of sharing certain information, please see the “Right to Opt Out” section below.

G-III FAMILY. We are part of the G-III Apparel Group, Ltd. (“G-III”) corporate family. We refer to G-III and its affiliates within this Privacy Policy as the “G-III Family.” A list of current members of the G-III Family is located at www.g-iii.com. We may transfer information to other members of the G-III Family. We will share this information for our business purposes, including for order fulfillment, and to otherwise engage in the activities described in this Privacy Policy.

BUSINESS TRANSFER. We may share information with a successor to all or part of our business as permitted by law. For example, if part of our business was sold, customer lists may be shared as part of that transaction.

SERVICES AND PROMOTIONS. We may share information with third parties who perform services on our behalf and help operate our Sites. We use third party partners to provide our e-commerce solution, operate the Sites, and help deliver our products and services. We also share information with vendors who send emails for us and who help deliver our products and services. We may also share information with third-party payment providers or companies that run a promotion on our behalf.

AGGREGATE STATISTICS. We may disclose information collected from multiple individuals in the form of aggregate data that does not describe or identify any individual user. This may include things like age and gender. It may also include product purchase information, search terms and pages visited. We may share such information with third parties to show interest in, and use of, our Sites.

FOR MARKETING PURPOSES. These third parties may include third parties who co-sponsor a promotion. They may also include third parties in whose products or services we believe you may be interested. These third parties may send you information about events and products by mail or email. These third parties may also share your information with others. These third parties may use the information for their own marketing purposes or the marketing purposes of others. This may include the delivery of interest based advertising.

LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES. We may link to other sites or apps or have third party services on our platforms we don’t control. If you click on a third party link, you will be taken to a platform we do not control. This policy does not apply to the privacy practices of that website or platform. We are not responsible for these third parties.

TO COMPLY WITH THE LAW OR PROTECT OURSELVES. We may disclose information if we believe it is required by law. We may also share information to enforce the terms of this Privacy Policy or our Terms of Use. We may also share information to protect the rights, property, or safety of DKC, our users, or others. We may share information to respond to a court order or subpoena or if a government agency or investigatory body requests. We may share your information with the US government. We might share information when we are investigating potential fraud.

We may share information for other reasons we may describe to you.

## YOU HAVE CERTAIN CHOICES ABOUT HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION.

RECEIVING CERTAIN TYPES OF CORRESPONDENCE. You can opt out of receiving our marketing emails. To stop receiving our promotional emails, follow the instructions in any promotional message you get from us or log in to your account and change your settings. Even if you opt out of getting marketing messages, we will still send you transactional messages. These include responses to your questions. If you object to our use of your information for direct marketing purposes, please email us at help@donnakaran.com.

TRACKING ACTIVITIES. You can control cookies and tracking tools. To learn how to manage how we – and our vendors – use cookies and other tracking tools, and to read our Do Not Track policy, please click here.

MOBILE. You can control certain tools on your mobile devices. For example, you can turn off the GPS locator or push notifications on your phone. 

## WHAT ARE YOUR ACCESS RIGHTS ?

You may correct or update your information at any time. You can do this by logging in to “My Account” on www.donnakaran.com. You can also call customer service at 866-984-2118 or email us at help@donnakaran.com. If you ask, we will send you a copy of any information we have on file in your user account. Before we are able to provide or change any information, we may ask that you verify your identify. We may also ask for more details to help us respond to your request.

## HOW DO WE SECURE YOUR INFORMATION ?

The Internet is not 100% secure. We cannot promise that your use of our sites will be completely safe. We encourage you to use caution when using the Internet. This includes not sharing your passwords. We keep personal information as long as it is necessary or relevant for the practices described in this Policy. We also keep information as otherwise required by law.

We may contact you if your information is compromised. If we have your e-mail address, we may notify you by e-mail.

## ARE CHILDREN ALLOWED TO USE DONNAKARAN.COM ?

Our Sites are meant for adults. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13 without permission from a parent or guardian. If you are a parent or legal guardian and think your child under 13 has given us information, you can email us. You can also write to us at the address listed at the end of this policy. Please mark your inquiries “COPPA Information Request.” Parents, you can learn more about how to protect children's privacy on-line here.

## CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

If you reside in California, you have the right to ask us one time each year if we have shared personal information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make a request, please send us an email, or write to us at the address listed below. Indicate in your letter that you are a California resident making a “Shine the Light” inquiry.

## POLICY UPDATES

From time to time we may change our privacy policies. We will notify you of any material changes to our Policy as required by law. We will also post an updated copy on our website. Please check our site periodically for updates.

## CONTACT US

You can contact us with question about this Policy. You may call us at (866) 984-2118 or email us at help@donnakaran.com. You can also send a request through the “Contact Us” feature on our Sites. If you have any questions about this Policy or want to access, delete, or correct your information, you can also email us at help@donnakaran.com.
